Hello hello friends hello
welcome to all of you in today's video in today's
video we are going to talk about
how to make a free credit
card bill in the bank, the online
process will go through so friends first of all I am
showing you in the description
you have to click on it as soon as you click on it
this whatsapp will open in front of you about
online this
is our website here anyone will give icic
free credit card debit card online so we will
teach you everything here now
how to apply for it and you will
get it I will let's click on fire
brigade records online
after clicking on it the
ICC credit card
website will open directly in front of you from where you can check it in minutes you will get it
here brother the
quantity is you have to enter university date
of birth salary dancer's video
you have to enter here what work you do
and we will put the money here the
payment comes in account transfer
how to get that check the PAN card number and if you
have any old account then you
can enter it here if you don't have then no
Make a relationship, later you will enter your name,
mobile number and email ID, if you have to, then there is a
little different company promo list below, you have to
enter the name of the company you work for, so I enter the
details and click on cement, so
friends, enter the side here
in the morning, click on submit, like Amit,
click on it, then I will show you here whether
you are in your life or not, I have
shown it here also and sorry
thanks for your work for interest in
SSC Bank credit card, if this is telling
brother, you are not a pimpl, if you
burn it for this, then you will be seen in it further,
you have to enter your name here
and whatever comment you have, the
CIC people will ask for it from here and you have to
enter it here, they will say that we cannot put
PAN card or any song or sewing on this, if
this thing is not right then we
cannot record you, so if
your kidney is not working in this match then you
can avoid fixing another match and
if you ask you to apply then it is
written in the description, see,
click on it  And you will also get my number, you
can contact me on that number and get your reply, so thank you friends,
thank you very much for watching the video,
if you liked the full video then do like, share and
subscribe, thank you friends.